Sumit Manshukhbhai Gohil

Mobile: 9824656823

Email: gohilsumit61@gmail.com

Seeking Manager level assignment in Automobile Industry in Service Field.

Professional Profile

A smart, mature, dynamic and result oriented professional in the automobile service industry with 06 years of extensive experience in Passenger car workshops. Started the career with a reputed passenger car dealer KATARIA AUTOMPBILES PVT.LTD in Ahmadabad as a Technician and rapidly progressed to the level of Service Advisor and then become an Asst. Works Manager at Ahmadabad Territory.

Resourceful at maintaining excellent relationship with workshop customers to ensure highest satisfaction levels by resolving their related critical issues. Skilful at training technicians & Service Advisor &monitoring their progress& motivating them to enhance their efficiencies & assist them to deliver quality services to clients. Good Relationship management, analytical & communication skills useful for workshop growth.

Academic Credentials

ITI - DLM

From Sola, Ahmadabad

- Certifications achieved in Maruti Suzuki India Ltd from their Training Centre at Ahmadabad, Mumbai ,Pune & also from MSIL Gurgaon Factory.
- I had successfully attended many training from Maruti Suzuki India Ltd in my career.
- Basic Training Course
- Communication Skills Training Course
- Advance Training Course
- Special Diagnostic Training Course
- Qualified in Master Certification Programme
- ENGINE OVERHAUL Training Course
- Soft Skill Level 1 & 2 Trained
- Training on All New model.

Core Competencies:

Automobile Industry (Service)

- Exceptional ability to collaborate with team members and teach new concepts in an effective manner.
- Internal quality management for automobile passenger car workshop.

❖ Fields of Experience

- Skilled Technician, Bronze & Silver Master.
- Smart and efficient Service Advisor in Passenger car workshop
- Vast Experience as a Technical field.
- Supervising and monitoring the performance levels of the technicians& Service Advisor.
- Organizing regular monthly &periodic meetings for entire team for discussing current work issues and devising solutions for enhanced workshop productivity & growth.

Career Highlights

Asst. Works Manager, Kataria Automobiles, AHMEDABAD The company is a leading Maruti Suzuki Authorized dealer in Gujarat. Continue From November 2016 to March 2017.

➤ I have started my Automobile career as a Customer care executive in Kataria Automobiles Pvt. Ltd

Workshop Technician, *Kataria Automobiles, AHMEDABAD' The company is a leading Maruti Suzuki Authorized dealer in Gujarat. From June 2006 to October 2009*.

➤ After 3 Years of experience, I was promoted as a Service Advisor in Kataria Automobiles Pvt. Ltd

Service Advisor, Kataria Automobiles, Ahmedabad The company is a leading Maruti Suzuki Authorized dealer in Gujarat. From Dec 2009 to Oct 2016 and till date.

The Role as an Asst. Works Manager

- Responsible for development and maintenance of quality control policies.
- Interacted with customers and clients to get feedback about the dealership service quality.
- To analyze customer complaints and find quality related solutions to improve service quality.
- To understand and note the complaints reported by customers.
- To ensure that all jobs requested by customer are completed in time.
- To take road trial of cars to check quality of work.
- Ensure washing quality & give delivery at promised time.
- Make follow up calls to customers for service quality feedback.
- Report to WM& GM also.
- To achieve monthly Repair order, Labor targets.
- Encourage the team to deliver better quality and productivity.

Personal Details:

Name : Sumit Gohil

Father Name : Mansukhbhai Gohil

Date of Birth : 24/09/1988

Gender : Male

Langue Known : English, Hindi, Gujarati

Marital Status : Married

Hobbies : Reading & Writing

Nationality : Indian

E-Mail ID : gohilsumit61@gmail.com
Permanent Address : A/16 Bhavna raw house part-2,

Ranip, Ahmedabad -382480

<u>Declaration</u>:I do hereby declare that the particulars of information and facts stated herein above are true, correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.

Date:-	(Sumit Gohil)
Place:	